Hey, Black Power, what's the reaction to your arrest, Mr. Brown?
Of course.
Wait since America has done it again, but that's not going to end the burning in burning in Detroit, brother,
because we built the country up and we'll burn it down, honkies and all.
Mr. Brown, did you tell them to burn down that school?
Be serious.
I ain't got to tell black folks what to burn.
Did you tell them to shoot Lady Bird?
Did I tell them to burn down Detroit?
Did I tell them to bring black people here?
Did you tell them to shoot Lady Bird?
I say they give me a gun and tell me to shoot my enemy.
I might shoot you.
Where have you been since the other night, baby?
Oh, well.
But a lot of you running around talking about you Democrats,
and the Democrats got you in the biggest trick going.
They tell you that our fault is the Dixocrats.
There's no such thing as the Dixocrats.
The only difference between George Wallace and Lyndon Johnson is one of them's wife got cancer.
He works off the military-industrial complex, which means that it's profitable to wage war.
And unless you, you know, devise another plan or another scheme to sustain or to boost this economy,
then it's going to be necessary to wage war, whether, you know, a black individual is in office or a white individual is in office.
So we're talking about a complete change in system.
If Mr. Cleaver did win the election, don't you think that he could have conducted the presidency in a unique manner
that may not be, you know, compromising to the system you speak of?
No, because, as I said, the system dictates the response to individuals.
You see, individuals do not influence, you know, politically, economically, or socially the attitudes of functioning of the system.
Well, if politics as we know it here in this country is not the answer, what is?
I think there has to be a re-evaluation of politics.
Now, there are definitions of politics that are relevant to black people.
Chairman Mao says that politics is war without bloodshed, and war is an extension of politics.
I think black people have to begin to address themselves to the politics of revolution.
Because we are caught up in a revolutionary struggle, whether we want to believe it or whether we want to be or not.
So I think, you know, black people have to begin to think in a revolutionary fashion
and create and construct a politically revolutionary platform.
People recognize, and the poor people recognize first, what it takes to get the man off your back,
what it takes to get freedom in America.
I say violence is necessary.
Violence is a part of America's culture.
It is as American as cherry pie.
American taught the black people to be violent.
Each time a police officer shoots and kills a black teenager, that is urban crime.
Black people have to begin to identify with the word black and with other black people, not Negroes.
You don't decide what I am.
You see, animals and slaves are named after and by their masters.
Men named themselves.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, baby, all right!
Better way to enslave a man than give him the vote and call him free.
See, it does not profit black people or poor people anything to have the vote and not be able to select the candidates who they want to choose.
Now, how can you choose between London, Johnson, Nixon, Agnew, Wallace, and Humphrey?
There is no choice.
Evil is evil.
There's nothing in between that.
There were some lesser candidates.
Gregory was running for office.
Eldridge Cleaver.
I think the vote can only be used as a tool of organization.
We can only use the vote to organize our people.
Now, to really believe that we can put someone in office and that these people would be responsive to our needs is naive, politically naive.
Because even if one of the black candidates who ran for office were to take the office of president, then black people must be prepared to fight against that person.
Because, you see, the system mandates the action of the individual.
The individual does not determine how this country will function.
This country works off the military-industrial complex, which means that it's profitable to wage war.
And unless you, you know, devise another plan or another scheme to sustain or to boost this economy, then it's going to be necessary to wage war.
Whether, you know, a black individual is in office or a white individual is in office.
Well, we're talking about a complete change in system.
You see, we recognize America for what it is, the Fourth Reich.
And we tell America to be on notice because if you are going to play Nazis, black folks ain't going to play Jews.
DC and Baltimore, you're up next.
I'm outside, y'all, doing what I can to decolonize minds on my mission-driven book tour for my new book, What Would the Ancestors Say?
They say books won't change the world.
Tell that to every colonizer that burned them.
Come on out, be in community, buy a book, and get it signed.
RSVP at amandaseals.com